Denys Ishchenko

Nikolayev, Ukraine

Age: 24;

Marital status: single; Phone№: +380930843911; E-mail: idemos14@gmail.com;

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/denys-ishchenko-554a6374;

GitHub: https://github.com/DIsh14;

Skype: den_ish.



Summary:

I'm purposeful, ambitious, persistent, communicative, result-oriented team player, who is able to make quick decisions and adapts well to new situations. I'm stress resistant and can work under pressure and tight deadlines. I always try to improve my skills and to learn new.

I'm a quick learner and have experience in content management for 1,5 year, in analytics and preparing reports for 1,5 year and 1 year in Frontend.

My goal is to join <u>Junior Frontend position</u> in the major international IT-company and to become high-qualified <u>Senior Web Developer</u>.

- Skills:
- Analytics: MS Excel, PowerPoint;
- WebUI: HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery, AngularJS, Grunt, Bower;
- Data Bases and Data Programming: MS SQL Server, NetSuite, T-SQL, MySQL;
- OOP;
- <u>UML</u>: Conceptual, logical, class, state diagrams;
- Git;
- **Projects:** http://barveneciya.com/ presentation site for the restaurant.
 https://dish14.github.io/angularjs-dynamic-application/ test project on AngularJS with saving data in the browser local storage.
- Languages: Russian (Native speaker), Ukrainian (Advanced), English (Intermediate);
- Interests: movies, books, marketing, active rest, WebUI, OOP, QA.

Job Experience:

• Edvantis, Lviv, Ukraine June 2016 – September 2016

Position: Software Development Intern.

Job description: Edvantis BootCamp. 3-months full-time courses.

Creating Single Page Application online-shop project "DressLine" in the team of 4 members using AngularJS, Bootstrap on Frontend and Spring MVC, Hibernate, MySQL on Backend. Learning such technologies as:

- Software Development Fundamentals;
- Software Architecture and Design;
- Object Oriented Programming;
- Relational Data Programming;
- Web UI Programming;
- Java Platform;

- Quality Assurance Theory.

• Private Entrepreneur, contract with Onyx Enterprises, Nikolayev, Ukraine March 2015 – June 2016 (1 year 4 months)

Position: Warehouse Support Specialist and Analyst.

Job description: Providing instructions online to warehouse in NJ location.

Online inventory, online purchasing items from vendors, creating shipping instructions, working with the returns (determining the cause of the returns and it's further processing, getting credits from the vendors for the returned items, problem solving with the damaged or defective items), generating monthly sales, profit, stock and analytics reports, correspondence with the warehouse team via Skype and e-mail.

I worked in Netsuite database and created reports using SQL requests.

• Private Entrepreneur, contract with Onyx Enterprises, Nikolayev, Ukraine September 2013 – November 2014 (1 year 3 months)

Position: Content Manager.

Job description: Adding, updating products on the company website (www.carid.com/).

Massive upload products using .csv files. Prices, descriptions, images update, managing categories and brand pages, US auto parts manufacturers analytics, correspondence with the managers of manufacturing companies via e-mail, writing technical tasks to designers and copywriters.

I structured and sorted data from big ACES (Aftermarket Catalog Exchange Standard) files, manufacturer's blueprints and price lists using MS Excel formulas, created .csv files and uploaded all data on the website.

Education:

• Admiral Makarov National University of Shipbuilding, Nikolayev, Ukraine

September 2008 – March 2014

Major: Automatic systems engineering.

Main Subjects: Theory of Automatic Systems, Computer Science, Theory of Electronics, Technical English.

I earned Specialist Degree.

• Nikolayev Maritime Lyceum, Ukraine;

September 2004 – June 2008

Extended learning of Mathematics, Informatics and English.

Courses and trainings:

- Advanced study of Microsoft Excel at Onyx Enterprises;
- Software Testing Fundamentals (Prometheus Lviv IT School);
- WEB UI programming fundamentals (Prometheus Lviv IT School). Certificate link: https://github.com/DIsh14/Docs/blob/master/Certificate%20Web%20UI%20Prometheus%20100%25. pdf